

Yerlin Rojas

Junior Developer

PROFILE My passion for programming has strengthened as I have explored its possibilities and have been able to develop small applications and personal projects. Solving problems by writing code fascinates me and I enjoy the challenges that come with it. Experienced in creating custom projects for clients. I specialize in the development of attractive and functional websites, web applications and online stores.

Freelance

PROFESSIONAL Junior Full Stack | NOW

EXPERIENCE

REACT | JAVASCRIPT | HTML | CSS

Proyect: Mesón De Luz- E-commerce | Ene 2023- May 2023

Front-end development under React.js technology, back-end support

Erikana S.A

Junior Developer | 2019 - NOW

JAVASCRIPT | HTML | CSS

Support in the creation of user interfaces using HTML and CSS implementing JavaScript. Participation in the maintenance and updating of existing websites. Testing and solving minor problems.

Studio Arqubeit

Arquitecta BIM | 2017 - 2019

REVIT | AUTOCAD | BIM | NAVISWORKS

Development of architectural projects for foreign clients, design creation and restructuring of interior and exterior spaces for commercial and residential, urban and suburban buildings

EDUCATION

Full Stack Developer

Instituto CoderHouse | Now, Buenos Aires, Argentina

JavaScript / React

Instituto CoderHouse | 2023, Buenos Aires, Argentina TOP 10 PROYECTS

Desarrollo Web

Instituto CoderHouse | 2022, Buenos Aires, Argentina TOP 10 PROYECTS

Diplomado Implantación BIM

Universidad Central de Venezuela | 2021, Caracas, Venezuela

Arquitecta

Universidad Santa Maria | 2011 - 2018, Caracas, Venezuela

https://github.com/YerlinRojas **PROYECTS**

> SKILL HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT | DESARROLLO WEB | ILLUSTRATOR | PHOTOSHOP |

SASS | GITHUB | NODE.JS | EXPRESS

LANGUAGE Spanish: Native

English: Avance